Husky: wouw wouw wouw...
Husky: hey you....
Husky: what are you doing there ...??
Husky: are you sleeping again?
Husky: you are so lazy...
Husky: sleeping all the time....
Husky: you will be fat soon
Husky: look at me, i am looking so good
Other Dog: shut up !
Husky: shut up yourself !
Husky: you are stupid ...
Husky: yes you are....
Husky: i am the prettiest here and always will be
Husky: i am beautiful, clever and irresistible...
Husky: say something
Husky: you dont know what to say, because i am right...
Husky: you wish, you were like me...
Husky: Yes , you do....
Husky: you know what ??
Husky: even guys on the street...
Husky: the stupid guys, you know...
Husky: do you know what they are saying..??
Husky: they are saying: "uuuaahh uuuuouooh"
Other Dog: ( is she right...?? )
Husky: you should take a bath soon... wou wou wou
Husky: you stink like hell
Husky: take a shower, now.. go !
Husky: YOU STINK !
Other Dog: not true
Other Dog: I take bath every day
Other Dog: even conditioner
Husky: no you DONT !!
Husky: you fool
Other Dog: WHAT are you saying ??..
Other Dog: i smell like a rose.
Other Dog: Everybody knows....
Other Dog: you are jealous ...
Other Dog: what a bullshit....
Other Dog: I am getting tired ....
Other Dog: You stink
Husky: Stop IT !
Husky: never ..!
[Text on screen: forever love ...??? ;D]